<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">JWalk</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="lorem">Pug post-ironic occupy Tonx, PBR tattooed master cleanse stumptown you probably haven\'t heard of them selfies. Food truck Carles keytar, meggings mixtape gluten-free aesthetic normcore farm-to-table. Schlitz mustache kitsch, kale chips vegan 3 wolf moon Vice keytar single-origin coffee kogi. Bicycle rights slow-carb stumptown vegan fashion axe photo booth. Ennui cray cred cliche master cleanse, crucifix meggings readymade Truffaut. High Life cred bespoke leggings Tonx, disrupt bitters four loko YOLO Neutra asymmetrical bicycle rights vinyl. Authentic church-key wolf, dreamcatcher slow-carb locavore tousled.

Blue Bottle umami synth, Odd Future typewriter yr cliche mustache bespoke mixtape. Viral kale chips tousled fingerstache banh mi, synth ugh semiotics pop-up narwhal twee beard Austin scenester. Pork belly Blue Bottle Tumblr hella VHS Austin. Stumptown irony seitan Godard beard brunch. Organic dreamcatcher chillwave photo booth next level, skateboard try-hard fixie. Godard ethical tousled drinking vinegar selvage. Normcore ethical fixie scenester master cleanse Shoreditch gastropub literally cardigan.

Letterpress 8-bit quinoa umami ennui. Banjo normcore Cosby sweater, kitsch keytar letterpress photo booth farm-to-table Brooklyn artisan Blue Bottle PBR. Umami shabby chic disrupt, pug before they sold out Truffaut retro tofu artisan pop-up mumblecore wayfarers tote bag. Authentic biodiesel mlkshk, tote bag Wes Anderson mumblecore mustache ennui chambray Godard. Bushwick try-hard narwhal High Life, pork belly Brooklyn tattooed normcore. Carles wayfarers Schlitz tote bag, whatever lomo kale chips. Dreamcatcher polaroid blog selfies keytar.

Direct trade Echo Park try-hard, authentic DIY sartorial paleo. Helvetica typewriter meh, Godard gentrify Brooklyn salvia. Gastropub Intelligentsia skateboard fap VHS Portland, farm-to-table banh mi Thundercats authentic. 90\'s lo-fi hashtag, bespoke roof party messenger bag scenester shabby chic High Life. Keytar brunch viral Tonx 3 wolf moon chillwave beard paleo. Ennui irony retro yr raw denim. Ethical Marfa bitters, wayfarers Echo Park swag polaroid meggings leggings Shoreditch brunch hoodie.</string>
</resources>
